MOSTAFA KHAIRALLA

 \vee

mostafakhairalla789@gmail.com

**** +201093511748

♀ Egypt

ດ

https://github.com/MOSTAFA-khairalla

Talented Full Stack .NET

Developer Interested in Power Platform |OutSystems with 2years of experience leading projects through all phases of software development life cycle while maintaining strict deadlines. Improve functionality and performance by troubleshooting and analyzing systems to identify bugs and develop solutions. Skilled in implementing technologies including C#, ASPX, .NET

Framework, SQL Server, and VS

Skills

Code

Languages: C#

Web :HTML5, CSS,Java Script , Angular10, Jquery , ASP.NET (Core, MVC and Web Forms)

Services: ASP.Net MVC API, REST APIWeb and Application Servers: IIS, Apache

Frameworks: .NET Framework, Entity Framework

Design Patterns: Singleton, MVC, MVVM, Repository SDLC

Databases: Oracle, SQL Server Agile Tools: Visual Studio, VS Code

Education

Faculty of Specific
Education 2016
Department of to 2020
University
Overall Grade: Very Good
Graduation Project Grade:
Excellent Graduation year: 2020

Employment

EGMaster

Full Stack Dot Net Developer

I'm currently working on Building an ERP system

Business Eco System

Dot Net Developer

Cairo Oct. 2021

Alexandria

June 2022 to Current

Designed conceptual data model based on the requirement.

Developed charts for dashboards that shows the performance of point of sale program

Handled performance tuning.

Manipulated database for testing using SQL.

Created Roles By using Asp.net Core

Created master data management

Created Role's and authentication from scratch

Created reports by using RDLC

Impress Digital Solution

Full Stack Dot Net Developer

Dubai Oct. 2020 to Nov. 2021

Sharjah Investors Center

- •Migrated Sharjah Investors Center From Web Form To asp Dot net Core
- designing reports and invoices by using Report Viewer
- Designed and implemented user interfaces By using C#
- -Designing App main view using HTML, CSS, Java Script , JQuery

Projects

Graduation Project (Attendance QR Code System)

Mar. 2020 to Oct. 2020

June 2020 to Sept. 2020

Technologies & Tools used (Html,Css,Java Script ,Jquery, Bootstrap, C#, Entity framework, Mvc5, MS SQL server ,)) helps students to register attendance through Qr Code technology and through the program they can learn about attendance and absence

- •Designing Web System
- •Implementing new features and fixing problems
- •Designing SQL Database
- •Designing views using HTML, CSS.Java Script ,Jquery, Bootstrap

Educational Platform:

 $\label{thm:constraints} \textbf{Technologies} \ \& \ \textbf{Tools} \ \textbf{used} \ \textbf{(analysis and Designed application system to Help Students and Designed application system)} \ \textbf{(analysis and Designed application)} \ \textbf{(analysis analysis and Designed application)} \ \textbf{(analysis analysis and Designed application)} \ \textbf{(analysis analysis analysis$

Teachers, Html,Css,Java Script ,Jquery, Bootstrap, C#, Entity

framework, Mvc5, MS SQL server)

- Designing Web System
- •Implementing new features and fixing problems
- •Designing SQL Database
- •Designing App main view using HTML, CSS.Java Script ,Jquery, Bootstrap

ProDinner

Web application for restaurant management

Technologies & Tools used (Html,Css,Java Script ,Jquery, Bootstrap, C#, Entity

framework, Mvc5, MS SQL server)

- Analyzed requirements and designed application and database schema.
- •Designing views using HTML, CSS.Java Script ,Jquery, Bootstrap
- Coded, tested, debugged, and deployed applications

News Site

Technologies & Tools used (Html,Css,Java Script ,Jquery, Bootstrap, C#, Entity framework, asp.net core , MS SQL server)

- Analyzed requirements and designed application and database schema.
- •Designing views using HTML, CSS.Java Script ,Jquery, Bootstrap
- · Coded, tested, debugged, and deployed applications

Online Shopping Site

Technologies & Tools used (Html,Css,Java Script,Jquery, Bootstrap, C#, Entityframework, asp.net core, MS SQL server)

- Analyzed requirements and designed application and database schema.
- •Designing views using HTML, CSS.Java Script ,Jquery, Bootstrap
- Coded, tested, debugged, and deployed applications

Activities